# MICHAEL GOMEH

## FRONTEND | UX/UI | GAME DEVELOPER (4+ YRS)



## CONTACT

+972-587359757

gomehmichael@gmail.com

Pardes Hana, Israel

linkedin.com/in/michael-gomeh

#### SKILLS

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

React, NextJS, Javascript, Typescript, Redux Toolkit, REST API, Express

#### **GAME DEVELOPMENT**

Unreal Engine (Blueprints, C++), Pixel Streaming, 3D Product Development

### UI/UX & DESIGN

CSS, Tailwind, UI Frameworks, Figma, Adobe Photoshop

#### **ADDITIONAL TECHNOLOGIES**

Git, Perforce, Plastic SCM, AWS, Bash, VSCode, Webstorm, Vercel, Netlify

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Autodidact Training**

Self-directed learning focused on advanced software engineering principles, game development techniques, and emerging technologies.

#### LANGUAGES

Hebrew - Native, English - Fluent

#### **PROFILE**

Frontend Developer with 4+ years of experience in JavaScript, React, CSS, Flutter, Unreal Engine and Kotlin, with a background in 3D product development and interactive design, I specialize in crafting intuitive, responsive applications from concept to deployment, leveraging skills in React to build cohesive, user-focused solutions. experienced in cross team collaboration, resulting in polished, efficient user experiences. With a keen eye for UI/UX design, I bring a unique blend of frontend expertise, 3D experience, agile practices, and a commitment to innovation.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (4+ YRS)

## Frontend Engineer | Unreal Developer

2023 - Present

Tweaks AI, Tel Aviv

- Built from scratch a responsive web application, combining 2D and 3D elements using React and Unreal Engine 5
- Managed a structured development process, turning concepts into engaging and efficient user interface.
- Collaborated with frontend, backend, and product teams to ensure smooth integration and a unified user experience.
- Built custom tools and components using REST APIs to enhance the interactive features of the application.
- Automated the deployment process on AWS for easier and more reliable software releases.

## Frontend Engineer | Unreal Developer

2022 - 2023

ByondXR, Herzliya

- Developed immersive web applications for 3D stores using React and Unreal Engine, enhancing online shopping with photorealistic, panoramic 3D experiences.
- Built automation tools in Python to streamline image processing workflows and optimize 3D environments.
- Collaborated closely with interdisciplinary teams to deliver highimpact, innovative solutions.

## Unreal Engine Game Developer

Multiverse Labs, Singapore

2021 - 2022

- Developed innovative Unreal Engine games and simulations for a Massive Metaverse experience.
- Collaborated with artists and designers to create compelling visuals and interactive gameplay mechanics.

Nerd148, Netanya

• Designed & Developed Unreal Engine games, including NFT and blockchain integration to open-world 3D game.

## Freelance Experience

Worldwide 2019 - 2021

- Built web projects and apps using various technologies
- Lead Unreal Developer for Virtuo Studios (Virtual Reality Symphony Orchestra).
- Indie Composer and Sound Designer for video games and films.
- Unreal Engine Tutor.